<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Aleksandra</title>
    <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me" />
    <updated>2022-11-08T21:24:00+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Aleksandra Lakić</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://alekslakic.github.io/me</id>

    <entry>
        <title>About me</title>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Lakić</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/about-me.html"/>
        <id>https://alekslakic.github.io/me/about-me.html</id>

        <updated>2022-11-08T19:34:17+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/4/aleks4.jpeg" alt="" />
                    Project manager with experienced in developing, implementing and coordinating programs and projects. Strong competencies in organizing teams and allocating resources in compliance with project goals and objectives. Administrative and communication proficiency. Looking forward to show you my work
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/4/aleks4.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p>Project manager with experienced in developing, implementing and coordinating programs and projects. Strong competencies in organizing teams and allocating resources in compliance with project goals and objectives. Administrative and communication proficiency. </p>
<p>Looking forward to show you my work</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>My Publications</title>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Lakić</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/my-publications.html"/>
        <id>https://alekslakic.github.io/me/my-publications.html</id>

        <updated>2022-05-26T17:38:04+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/2/2knjige.png" alt="" />
                <figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/2/2knjige-2.png" sizes="(min-width: 61.3125em) 50vw, 100vw" srcset="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/2/responsive/2knjige-2-xs.png 300w ,https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/2/responsive/2knjige-2-sm.png 480w ,https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/2/responsive/2knjige-2-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="3258" height="1679"></figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>21st Century Self-management</title>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Lakić</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/21st-century-self-management.html"/>
        <id>https://alekslakic.github.io/me/21st-century-self-management.html</id>
            <category term="Srpski"/>
            <category term="Books"/>

        <updated>2022-05-27T17:43:09+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    "The experience of Yugoslav self-governing socialism is a unique example of a broad, systemic application, of economic democracy principles, aiming to achieve greater participation of employees in economic decision-making, decentralisation of ownership and social reproduction beyond market."&nbsp;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    "The experience of  Yugoslav self-governing socialism is a unique example of a broad, systemic application, of economic democracy principles, aiming to achieve greater participation of employees in economic decision-making, decentralisation of ownership and social reproduction beyond market."&nbsp;
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/1/2knjige-2.png" sizes="(min-width: 61.3125em) 50vw, 100vw" srcset="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/1/responsive/2knjige-2-xs.png 300w ,https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/1/responsive/2knjige-2-sm.png 480w ,https://alekslakic.github.io/me/media/posts/1/responsive/2knjige-2-md.png 768w"  height="1679" width="3258" alt="" />
      
    </figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Are there green jobs in Serbia?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksandra Lakić</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/green-jobs-in-serbia.html"/>
        <id>https://alekslakic.github.io/me/green-jobs-in-serbia.html</id>
            <category term="Srpski"/>
            <category term="Articles"/>

        <updated>2022-11-08T21:24:00+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Original title: Ima li u Srbiji zelenih poslova? The article deals with the process of green transition in Serbia and its effetcs on the labour market. Faced with the growing threath of ecological and climate changes on one hand, and the pressure of the international&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Original title:<br><strong>Ima li u Srbiji zelenih poslova?</strong></p>
<p>The article deals with the process of green transition in Serbia and its effetcs on the labour market. Faced with the growing threath of ecological and climate changes on one hand, and the pressure of the international community as well as the local activist groups and movemnts on the other, Serbian government has been pushed to imlement meassures facilitating transition toward the sustainale economy. The article discusses the progress Serbia has made in adoppting and implmenting those meassures, including various factors, both socio-political and economic that influnce the pace of transformation. Besides, it focuses on the effects these meassures might have in adressing challneges the green transition might have on the workers and the quality of emolyment. Conclusions drawn from the analysis of the public policies adopted until now and the reflection on the structural factors influencing their effects, call for the action on behalf of decision makers, progressive movements and social actors to take a more decisevie action in order to be able to tackle more effectively both the enviormental and socio-economic challenges posed by the current processes and developments. </p>
<p><strong>Published by</strong> portal Mašina<strong>, <a href="https://alekslakic.github.io/me/green-jobs-in-serbia.html" title="https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;rls=en&amp;q=ma%C5%A1%C5%A1ina+ima+li+u+srbiji+zelenih+poslova&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8">link</a></strong></p>
<h4 class="p1"> </h4>
<p class="p1"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
